Hey, Roxanne.
I want to add skills to my equipment.
How do I do that?
Normally you purchase gear that
comes with skills equipped.
I'm not talking about buying equipment.
How do I add them myself?
Are you talking about Skill Crystals?
Skill Crystals?
They're formed through the
accumulation of monster skills.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
They're found rarely in labyrinths,
and when fused with equipment...
It applies that skill?
It all depends on the skill of
the blacksmith fusing the items.
A blacksmith, huh? I'll need that job.
How can I become one?
I'm sorry, but Blacksmith
is a job unique to dwarves.
You aren't eligible.
I can't become one?!
So I'll have to hire a blacksmith if I
want to make any equipment with skills.
I wouldn't recommend it.
It fails most of the time,
and blacksmiths dislike direct transactions.
Even if you found one,
there's no telling if you can trust them.
Some dwarves have made a fortune by
pretending the fusion process failed.
I see.
They tell their client they failed and make a
profit selling the equipment with skills later.
Sounds like fusing Skill Crystals
is a source of a lot of problems.
Yes, Master. Though it's a different story
if you're on friendly terms with a blacksmith.
Then we'll recruit a blacksmith to our party.
What?
Nothing. Mind if I open the window?
That's fine.
Thank you for waiting.
Roxanne really is beautiful.
Roxanne, take this leather armor.
Yes, Master. Thank you.
Roxanne, were you able to get it on okay?
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Um...
I know equipment stretches and
shrinks to fit the wearer,
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
but this is too much.
Thank you.
I guess leather armor isn't for women.
It looks like the jacket
doesn't emphasize her figure.
Party Organization, Roxanne.
Select Target
[Party]
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Shall we get going?
Yes, Master.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Vale, Vale Plaza
Master, aren't we going to the labyrinth?
Teleport.
Huh? Um...
Huh? What?
Are you okay, Roxanne?
Master, where are we?
Vale Labyrinth, First Floor
On the first floor of the labyrinth.
But I thought Dungeon Walk could
only be used inside labyrinths.
I used Teleportation magic.
I've never heard of that.
It's possible not many others can
use it, so don't tell anyone.
Master, you're amazing.
Which way should we go?
Master, if you're looking for monsters,
there are some nearby to the right.
I can smell them.
What? You can?
I don't smell anything unusual.
Is it because you're a wolfkin?
My nose is exceptionally good, even for a wolfkin.
I'm good at detecting prey.
That's amazing.
Then could you take us towards the monsters?
Very well.
In that case, could you
lend me a Magic Crystal?
Magic Crystal? What's that?
Monsters are made of magic power.
When monsters are defeated,
their magic power gradually accumulates,
eventually forming a Magic Crystal.
Magic Crystals filled with magic power are
used by guild temples as energy sources.
Why do you want me to lend you one?
Because you can't store magic power when you
defeat monsters unless you have a Magic Crystal.
Have I been screwing myself?
Do Magic Crystals sell for a lot?
They're probably the most valuable item
that can be acquired in labyrinths.
Well, they're valuable,
but you only accumulate a
tiny amount of magic power at a time.
A person sells Magic Crystals only a handful
of times over the course of their life.
Even if you haven't had one
until now, you didn't lose much.
So it's all right.
Roxanne...
I made her concerned about me.
How can we acquire a Magic Crystal?
You can find them in labyrinths or
purchase empty ones from guilds.
Then, let's go buy some later.
Hey, there really was a monster.
Here I go.
I got it.
A single blow?
Impressive, Master.
It's this sword that's impressive.
Don't tell anyone.
Which way next?
Straight ahead.
She's happy?
All right. Let's keep going a little longer.
Vale, Vale Restaurant
You're the reason we got all of this.
Not at all.
We were able to defeat so many
because you're so strong, Master.
No, it's your power that's impressive.
Because I was a newcomer to the
party I used to be part of,
nobody listened to my opinions.
I either watched battles from a distance
or was told to attack inconspicuously
from behind, but you...
Well... You've got a great power.
We'd better put it to good use.
Yes, Master. I'm glad I
could be useful to you.
Come here and have a seat.
Yes, Master.
From now on, when we enter the room,
you don't need to wait to be told to sit.
Actually, sit as close to me as possible.
I'll try not to climb on top of you
just because you're sitting next to me.
I-I'm fine. I wouldn't mind—
I like the sound of that.
Can I taste your ears?
What? I-I doubt they taste very good.
I'm just going to play with them.
I'll stop if it hurts or you don't like it.
Let me know right away.
Actually, it feels good to have them stroked.
Would it be all right to eat them after all?
Anyway, these dog ears
reminds me of something.
Not sponge cake, but something springier.
Oh, I know.
Do they have grilled seaweed-wrapped
mochi around here?
Grilled seaweed-wrapped mochi?
It's a food I like from my homeland.
I don't know about around here,
but if you head to the coast,
you might find people
grilling fish on the beach.
Yeah, that's not quite the same thing.
I see. Maybe I'll try looking for some.
Um, Master...
Will you be returning to
your homeland someday?
My homeland, huh?
I know. I should've been
thinking about it, but...
I'm not going back.
And besides, I probably can't.
Unfortunately for you,
I won't be disbanding our party
so I can return to my homeland.
Actually, that's not why I asked.
I know.
Typically people sell slaves
they no longer need.
It's all right.
I plan on keeping you forever.
Yes, Master. Thank you.
But naturally, I do want to
maximize our party's strength.
I'll probably recruit more members.
Yes, Master. It's only natural.
Great. I'll take that to
mean she consents to forming a harem.
Two Magic Crystals, please.
Are black Magic Crystals acceptable?
Black?
I'd like empty crystals, please.
Those would be black Magic Crystals.
They're ten nars per crystal.
Roxanne,
thanks for waiting. Here they are.
A Magic Crystal's color changes depending
on the magic power stored inside it.
They turn red after defeating ten monsters
and purple after defeating a hundred.
So the color changes with
each tenfold increase.
Is there a maximum limit?
Apparently, they turn white after
defeating one million monsters,
but most stop at green,
which is ten thousand.
It's typical for people to sell
them once they turn blue,
after defeating 100 thousand monsters.
Got it. Then, let's head to the labyrinth.
All right.
Impressive. The first floor monsters
no longer stand a chance against you.
Why don't we head to a higher floor?
You mean it doesn't go down?
It goes upwards because
the labyrinth is growing.
What?
The labyrinth is growing?
Labyrinths are thought
to be living creatures.
They lure people to them,
use monsters to defeat them,
and feed on their bodies.
There are labyrinths other than this
one because the labyrinths multiplied.
How do you defeat—no, kill a labyrinth?
The only way is to defeat the boss on
every level and reach the highest floor.
Sounds like a tough battle.
I should think about acquiring ways
to attack multiple monsters at once.
Which means...
Are there any spells that attack all targets?
Spells? I've heard such spells exist,
but I don't know much about them.
If I want to become a Mage, I should
probably try actually casting spells.
I have Bonus Incantations
I can use without being a Mage.
I may be able to acquire the Mage job
by casting the attack spells
in my Bonus Incantations.
Gamma Ray Burst
Meteor Crash
I'll start with this one.
In that case...
Meteor Crash
Extreme Drop Dead
Self-Destruct
Equivalent Exchange
Character Settings
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
Gamma Ray Burst
I'm not done yet.
I must not have enough MP to cast it yet.
Master, that needle wood
was our tenth monster.
How is your Magic Crystal looking?
It changed color.
What about yours?
Mine is still black.
Only the person who strikes the
killing blow gains its magic power.
I didn't notice earlier,
but I have something called
Crystallization Upgrade as a Bonus Skill.
Crystallization Upgrade
Character Settings
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
Unlock Level Limit
Unlock Damage Limit
Unlock Party Settings
Crystallization Upgrade x32
This way.
It's probably a Magic Crystal-related buff.
Right.
x32...
Left.
Should be enough.
Roxanne, take a look.
Purple? But how?
Don't tell anyone.
Master, that's incredible.
Do you know how much Magic Crystals sell for?
Greens go for ten thousand nars,
and yellows go for 100 thousand nars.
It's not as though I need
the money right now,
so I guess I'll deactivate
Crystallization Upgrade.
Unlock Damage Limit
Unlock Party Settings
Unlock Party Settings?
It didn't matter when I was alone,
but now I'm grouping with Roxanne.
Unlock Damage Limit
Unlock Party Settings
Party Job Settings
I should test it out.
Party Job Settings.
Beast Warrior: Lv 6
Villager: Lv 8
Farmer: Lv 1
Warrior: Lv 1
Swordsman: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
So these are Roxanne's jobs.
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Beast Warrior: Lv 6
Villager: Lv 8
Farmer: Lv 1
Warrior: Lv 1
Swordsman: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Item Box
Beast Warrior seems to have good effects,
so I'll keep her the way she is.
That just leaves healing.
Do you have any healing skills or spells?
The Monk and Priest jobs can use those.
To become one, you must defeat
monsters with your bare hands.
Your bare hands?
But it seems worth trying out.
Roxanne, could you put away your
sword and fight bare-handed?
Yes, Master.
That said, it'll probably be
difficult even for the both of us
to defeat monsters bare-handed
from the get-go.
How was that?
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Farmer: Lv 1
Warrior: Lv 1
Swordsman: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Simply fighting bare-handed
isn't good enough.
But I don't know how long it'll take
if we fight bare-handed from the start.
I'll start with the killing blow only.
Durandal one-shots monsters, so...
Character Settings
Status
Bonus Equipment
Bonus Incantations
Bonus Skills
Weapon
●●●●●●
Accessories
○○○○○○
Identify
Fragarach
Offensive Power x5
HP Absorption
Incantation Interruption
You have all kinds of weapons.
I'll try this sword next.
I don't mind going at a turtle's pace.
Slow and steady does it.
Lowering my weapon's strength by
one level makes it ineffective?
Watch out, Rox—
Huh?
She's dodging all the monster's attacks.
At first glance, it seems like
she's barely dodging them,
but it's actually the other way around.
Large movements are inefficient.
Look, dodge, and attack.
It's like a magnificent dance.
Don't get distracted.
Now I just have to finish
it off with punches.
Warrior: Lv 10
Swordsman: Lv 8
Villager: Lv 5
Thief: Lv 3
Merchant: Lv 1
Huh? It's not there?
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Farmer: Lv 1
Warrior: Lv 1
Swordsman: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Monk: Lv 1
Roxanne, did you kill it?
Yes, Master. It was defeated when
I struck it after you punched it.
Impressive work.
You dodged all its attacks, too.
Because we had it surrounded.
And those attacks can be dodged
easily if you're watching closely.
Yeah, I don't think so.
I'll finish off the next one.
Roxanne, just help me
flank it and don't attack.
Understood.
This way.
If I want to get its health as low as
possible with a single sword attack,
then I need to adjust my Strength stat.
Status
Kaga Michio
Endurance
Spirit
Strength
Intelligence
Agility
Forty-five.
That was too much.
How about 20?
Thirteen, maybe?
Okay, it wasn't defeated.
Roxanne.
I know.
Character Settings.
Status
Kaga Michio
Endurance
Spirit
Strength
Intelligence
Agility
I'll unequip my Bonus Weapons and put all
my points in increasing my Strength stat.
Status
Kaga Michio
Endurance
Spirit
Strength
Intelligence
Agility
Now I'll pour everything I've
got into this single blow.
It noticed me?
Either way, I'm too close
to evade its attack.
So I'll keep pushing forward.
I-I'm impressed.
You killed it in a single blow.
Character Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Monk: Lv 1
Effect: Minor Spirit Increase
Effect: Tiny MP Increase
Skill: Treat Wounds
That took forever.
Treat Wounds.
The pain went away.
From now on, I'll use my skill to
heal us if we're damaged by monsters.
You can do that?
Farmer: Lv 1
Warrior: Lv 1
Swordsman: Lv 1
Explorer: Lv 1
Monk: Lv 1
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
I just set your job to Monk, too.
1st   Monk: Lv 1
What?
My job is Beast Warrior.
I've never been a Monk.
It's uh, you know...
Don't tell anyone.
Amazing.
Vale, Vale Restaurant
Excuse me.
Good work today.
Yes, Master. You, too.
How did you feel about today's combats?
Did you notice anything strange
from your perspective?
The way you fought was impressive.
I'm sorry I wasn't very useful.
You were plenty useful at finding monsters.
And besides, your movements in
combat seemed reliable, too.
I look forward to fighting alongside you.
Yes, Master. You can count on me.
Your fingers are so elegant and soft.
Yours are large, Master.
I thought we were around the same age.
Is it because you're a man?
They're so sturdy.
I'm sure it's the same for most men
whether they're humans or wolfkin.
U-Um...
Don't worry about it.
But...
Trust your Master.
I can't allow you to do this for me.
It's okay.
Every time I scrub Roxanne,
the vibrations reach the tips,
making them jiggle.
I must calm these unruly peaks.
I haven't washed that yet.
It's sweaty and dirty.
Don't worry about it.
Raise your arm.
But I'm a slave.
I can't allow you to wash me.
I'm doing this because I want to.
And besides, we'll sweat
even more after this.
You're not wrong.
But that's not what I meant.
At least, allow me to wash your body first.
Then, maybe I'll have you
do that once I finish here.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I can clean that myself.
Could you wash my body, too?
Yes, Master.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I could never imagine this happening
in the world I came from.
But that's why I feel so alive.
There aren't any monsters, but there's
something about this room that feels off.
It's a waiting room.
A waiting room?
The first floor boss is beyond this door.
Let's go, Roxanne.
Yes, Master.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem